<?xml version="1.0"?>
<NPCSpeech xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <Scene1>
    <Speech0>
      Good morning. How can I help you?
    </Speech0>
    <Speech1>
      Yes, it is.
    </Speech1>
    <Speech2>
      May I have your name, please?
    </Speech2>
    <Speech3>
      Ah yes, Mr.B. Please take a seat and wait a moment. I’ll tell the manager secrectary, he will come down soon.
    </Speech3>
  </Scene1>
  <Scene2>
    <Speech0>
      Good morning, B. I’m A – Sales Manager of A Company.
    </Speech0>
    <Speech1>
      How're you doing?
    </Speech1>
    <Speech2>
      That’s good. Let’s start the interview. First of all, tell me a little bit about yourself.
    </Speech2>
    <Speech3>
      What are you looking for in a job?
    </Speech3>
    <Speech4>
      What are your strengths? Why should I hire you?
    </Speech4>
    <Speech5>
      OK. Now, let me ask you a few quick questions. You do not mind working long hours, do you?
    </Speech5>
    <Speech6>
      Can you handle pressure?
    </Speech6>
    <Speech7>
      Do you still have any questions for me?
    </Speech7>
    <Speech8>
      B, nice to meet you. Thank you for coming. We’ll send the interview result via email.
    </Speech8>
    <Speech9>
      Have a good day !
    </Speech9>
  </Scene2>
  <Scene3>
    <Speech0>
      Good morning. This is the first day for you to work here. I hope you’ll like your job.
    </Speech0>
    <Speech1>
      You’ll spend most of this week to be familiar with all the work in the office.
    </Speech1>
    <Speech2>
      The main duty is to keep the file in order.
    </Speech2>
    <Speech3>
      And you are responsible for answering the calls, then transferring or taking messages.
    </Speech3>
    <Speech4>
      If you have any question, you can ask me at anytime.
    </Speech4>
  </Scene3>
  <Scene4>
    <Speech0>
      Hi, there. My name is A. You’re new around here?
    </Speech0>
    <Speech1>
      Welcome aboard! This is your seat. Some office supplies have been prepared.
    </Speech1>
    <Speech2>
      If there’s anything I can do for you, let me know.
    </Speech2>
    <Speech3>
      That’s all right. I’ll try my best.
    </Speech3>
  </Scene4>
  <Scene5>
    <Speech0>
      Good morning!
    </Speech0>
    <Speech1>
      Yes, traffic wasn’t much today, so I made it to the office earlier.
    </Speech1>
    <Speech2>
      Well, about an hour or so.
    </Speech2>
    <Speech3>
      No, I take a public bus. It’s safer.
    </Speech3>
    <Speech4>
      It really depends.
    </Speech4>
  </Scene5>
  <Scene6>
    <Speech0>
      It’s time for lunch. Let’s go grab some food.
    </Speech0>
    <Speech1>
      Where do you want to go for lunch? I’m bored of the canteen.
    </Speech1>
    <Speech2>
      OK. But where shall we have lunch?
    </Speech2>
    <Speech3>
      That’s sound good! Let’s go.
    </Speech3>
  </Scene6>
  <Scene7>
    <Speech0>
      Can you cover me for a while?
    </Speech0>
    <Speech1>
      I’m going to the post.
    </Speech1>
    <Speech2>
      I’ll come back as soon as possible.
    </Speech2>
    <Speech3>
      Thank you so much !
    </Speech3>
  </Scene7>
  <Scene8>
    <Speech0>
      How do you do?
    </Speech0>
    <Speech1>
      Yes, it’s me. And you must be B?
    </Speech1>
    <Speech2>
      Well, let’s start.
    </Speech2>
    <Speech3>
      Anything else?
    </Speech3>
    <Speech4>
      Great! Let me take a quick look.
    </Speech4>
  </Scene8>
  <Scene9>
    <Speech0>
      Hey, is there anything news from the meeting ?
    </Speech0>
    <Speech1>
      How many people will be charge in this project?
    </Speech1>
    <Speech2>
      Great! I like the teamwork, all of us can make the most of ourselves. In that way, new idea will explode.
    </Speech2>
    <Speech3>
      What’s the first step?
    </Speech3>
    <Speech4>
      But C and D are absent now.
    </Speech4>
    <Speech5>
      Ok. I will inform them.
    </Speech5>
  </Scene9>
  <Scene10>
    <Speech0>
      We have to work overtime today.
    </Speech0>
    <Speech1>
      Today is the deadline. Let’s get it done even if we have to stay up all night.
    </Speech1>
    <Speech2>
      Yes, about twice a month.
    </Speech2>
    <Speech3>
      I’ve been accustomed to it.
    </Speech3>
    <Speech4>
      Of course, it’s 1.5 times for workday overtime, and 2 times for weekends.
    </Speech4>
  </Scene10>
  <Scene11>
    <Speech0>
      Well, I think it is time to call it a day.
    </Speech0>
    <Speech1>
      What time do you want to meet tomorrow morning?
    </Speech1>
    <Speech2>
      Oh, no. It’s too early.
    </Speech2>
    <Speech3>
      Yeah that’s great for me.
    </Speech3>
  </Scene11>
  <Scene12>
    <Speech0>
      Yes, come in and sit down.
    </Speech0>
    <Speech1>
      I’ve been paying attention to your performance since last year and I’m really impressed. You have done a perfect job and your project made mych profit for the company.
    </Speech1>
    <Speech2>
      Sure. I will inform the general manager about this with your application.
    </Speech2>
    <Speech3>
      OK. I estimate that your monthly gross salary will increase by 1,000 dollars.
    </Speech3>
  </Scene12>
  <Scene13>
    <Speech0>
      Thanks!
    </Speech0>
    <Speech1>
      I’m too happy to say any word to you.
    </Speech1>
    <Speech2>
      Ok. Thank you very much.
    </Speech2>
  </Scene13>
  <Scene14>
    <Speech0>
      Yes, please.
    </Speech0>
    <Speech1>
      Really? Why do you think like that?
    </Speech1>
    <Speech2>
      Have you been doing your best?
    </Speech2>
    <Speech3>
      I think I understand how you feel. I’m glad you told me. I will try to fit you in somewhere else.
    </Speech3>
  </Scene14>
  <Scene15>
    <Speech0>
      Yes, what’s up?
    </Speech0>
    <Speech1>
      I’m sorry to hear that. Is that serious?
    </Speech1>
    <Speech2>
      Don’t worry. It maybe a routine medical examination.
    </Speech2>
    <Speech3>
      Take it easy. I will arrange someone to take over your job.
    </Speech3>
    <Speech4>
      Wish your dad would get well soon.
    </Speech4>
  </Scene15>
  <Scene16>
    <Speech0>
      B, you really did a good job this time.
    </Speech0>
    <Speech1>
      Your project made much profit for the company.
    </Speech1>
    <Speech2>
      The board decided to give you a bonus.
    </Speech2>
    <Speech3>
      Congratulation !
    </Speech3>
  </Scene16>
  <Scene17>
    <Speech0>
      My visit has proved to be a fruitful one.
    </Speech0>
    <Speech1>
      I think half of the credit should go to you.
    </Speech1>
    <Speech2>
      You work with high efficiency. Never did I expect you to finish it in such a short time.
    </Speech2>
    <Speech3>
      I will recommend you as the marketing manager.
    </Speech3>
    <Speech4>
      I’m sure you will do better than the current manager.
    </Speech4>
  </Scene17>
  <Scene18>
    <Speech0>
      I’m so happy to hear about your promotion. Congratulations.
    </Speech0>
    <Speech1>
      What are your responsibilities with this new position?
    </Speech1>
    <Speech2>
      So I should call you marketing manager from now on.
    </Speech2>
    <Speech3>
      By the way, you are efficient. You deserve it.
    </Speech3>
  </Scene18>
  <Scene19>
    <Speech0>
      Here is our price sheet.
    </Speech0>
    <Speech1>
      Sure, take your time.
    </Speech1>
    <Speech2>
      You know that the cost of production has been skyrocketing in recent years.
    </Speech2>
    <Speech3>
      Well, we can consider making some concessions in our prices.
    </Speech3>
    <Speech4>
      To get the business done, we can reduce our prices by 5% .
    </Speech4>
    <Speech5>
      Yes, sir. Please take our offer to consideration. I hope we will have the opportunity to cooperate.
    </Speech5>
  </Scene19>
  <Scene20>
    <Speech0>
      Good morning mr.B !
    </Speech0>
    <Speech1>
      I'm really glad that you can meet me today to discuss the details of the order.
    </Speech1>
    <Speech2>
      Which model do you want to order and how many?
    </Speech2>
    <Speech3>
      Okay. Do you know our quoted price?
    </Speech3>
    <Speech4>
      That's correct.
    </Speech4>
    <Speech5>
      Perfect !!
    </Speech5>
  </Scene20>
  <Scene21>
    <Speech0>
      Yes, please.
    </Speech0>
    <Speech1>
      Could you tell me why you made the decision ?
    </Speech1>
    <Speech2>
      Are you certain? Your achievements were proved to be one of the best ones in this company. 
    </Speech2>
    <Speech3>
      OK. I will take your paper to consideration. Good luck! 
    </Speech3>
  </Scene21>
  <Scene22>
    <Speech0>
      B, I’ve heard you want to quit.
    </Speech0>
    <Speech1>
      Could I ask why you want to quit?
    </Speech1>
    <Speech2>
      Where do you want to go?
    </Speech2>
    <Speech3>
      Please still stay in touch with us.
    </Speech3>
    <Speech4>
      ...
    </Speech4>
  </Scene22>
</NPCSpeech>